http://www.toywiz.com/privacy-security/

close
Need your order delivered in time for the Holidays?
Please note that due to COVID-19 and its impact on UPS and the US Postal Service, these dates are best estimates for when you should order by and are are NOT guarantees. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee any specific delivery date at this time.
Holiday FAQ:
FOR BEST CHANCE OF CHRISTMAS DELIVERY BEFORE 12/25 ORDER BY:
Thursday, December 17th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Wednesday, December 16th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Tuesday, December 15th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Monday, December 14th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
FOR BEST CHANCE OF RUSH CHRISTMAS DELIVERY ARRIVING BEFORE 12/25 ORDER BY:
Sunday, December 20th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
FOR BEST CHANGE OF LAST NIGHT OF HANUKKAH DELIVERY BY 12/17 ORDER BY:
Thursday, December 10th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Wednesday, December 9th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Tuesday, December 8th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Monday, December 7th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
FOR BEST CHANGE OF RUSH LAST NIGHT OF HANUKKAH DELIVERY ARRIVING BEFORE 12/17 ORDER BY:
Sunday, December 13th, 11:59 PM Must choose UPS Next Day
Click here for more tips to help ensure there are no issues with your order.
Holiday Shipping Info
Hello,
DC Funko POP!
Movies Funko POP!
Television Funko POP!
Animation Funko POP!
Star Wars Funko POP!
Disney Funko POP!
Pez Dispensers
Five Nights at Freddy's
Games Funko POP!
Game of Thrones
Vynl.
DC Funko POP!
Marvel Funko POP!
Music Funko POP!
My Little Pony Funko POP!
WWE Wrestling POP!
Sports & UFC POP!
Funko 5 Star
FunkO's Breakfast Cereal
Pint Size Heroes Packs, Boxes
The Walking Dead
Wetmore Forest Funko POP!
Pets Funko POP!
Funko T-Shirts, Apparel & Lanyards
Wacky Wobblers, Hikari & Funko Force
MyMojis
The Vote & Assorted POP!
Funko Mystery Boxes & Lots
Candy & Food Funko POP!
Books Funko POP!
Marvel Funko POP!
Pokemon Just Added!
Star Wars Just Added!
Vintage Collection 3 3/4"
The Clone Wars (All Series)
Dragon Quest (Warrior)
Hi! This is our privacy policy and, if you landed here,
it means that you want to learn how we
process your personal data at
ToyWiz.com. We won’t let you down!
Essential
information we collect
In operating our store, it is essential for us to capture some
information about your device, such as
your IP address and information related to your visit when you browse
our store. For example, this
might include time-stamp, the last page or product you visited, the
indication that you logged in.
We do that in order to:
remember who you are after you log in so that you do
not need to authenticate at each
click;
monitor if our website is running with the high
performance we are dedicated to
providing;
let you browse between products without having to
start back from the home page at
each click;
display items or ads you might find
interesting;
remember if you put something in your shopping cart
before you decide to checkout; and
control that your data is processed securely.
We call the information mentioned above “essential information” and we
collect it through the
use of cookies. Cookies are small text files that most websites use. A
website places cookies in the
web browser and then reads the information collected through the
cookies every time the user
performs an action. We
use cookies. Without enabling this mechanism and this kind
of cookies
(first-party cookies), we could not provide you with the smooth
experience that you expect while
you are navigating.
Order information
you expressly
provide
If you buy something from our store, we will need more specific
information about you. To fully
process your order and ship the merchandise you selected, we need your
personal data such as
your first and last name, your email address and your shipping and
billing address. We also use
your contact and order information to send you communication related to
the processing of your
order. We will ask you to provide this information in our “checkout
page” before letting you
finalize your purchase with the payment.
Accounts
You can sign up for an account if you’d like. This will make us happy
because it confirms your
interest in our store. It should also make you happy because we will
remember your information
and, when you decide to buy our products, you do not have to provide
all of your information over
again -- you just have to log-in. Before registering your account, we
will ask you to expressly
provide your consent to this privacy policy. Only if you give us your
consent, we will open your
account. We also you the possibility to easily withdraw your consent
and delete your account. Just
connect with us at the contact details at the bottom of the page.
Partial Purchases
If you have started to buy one of our products, but have not completed
the purchase, you may
have provided partial information, such as your email. In that case, we
might send you an email to
remind you about your interest. If you are not comfortable in receiving
further emails of this kind,
we will give you a simple opportunity to opt-out. Your privacy means a
lot to us and we will stop
sending you these communications right away.
Reviews
If you have completed a purchase, we may send you an email to ask you
to review the product you
bought. We want to be sure that whether you love your purchase or have
a complaint, you can
share your opinion with other customers.
Personalization
We also use some specific information related to your visit, such as
the timestamp of your visit, the
page or the product you viewed, where you are coming from (if you came
to our store because you
clicked on an advertisement or you just opened our direct link). This
is very similar to the
“essential information,” but we use it to provide you with a
personalized experience. The
information on your visit provides us with insights on your interests
and allows us to send you
relevant communications. We capture this information through cookies,
called a "beacon."
Newsletters
& Emails
If you sign up for our newsletters and product updates, we will use the
information you provide to us to send regular newsletters. If you have
updated your subscription profile with product preferences or if you've
purchased from our shop, you may also receive email alerts targeted to
your preferences and/or your purchase history.
How do we process
your information?
We use an external provider to run our store, BigCommerce . BigCommerce
is based in the US and
is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and committed to
providing best-in-class
service and data protection. You can check its participation in the
Privacy Shield on the
official site of The International Trade Administration (ITA), U.S.
Department of Commerce.
11305 Four Points Drive / Building II, Third Floor / Austin, TX 78726,
or contact them at privacy@bigcommerce.com
Through BigCommerce, we also use other, highly specialized external
providers to provide the
most competitive services. For example:
Payment: Our store is PCI-DSS compliant (a very
strict industry standard with
requirements for the security of credit card information), and we use
an accredited
company to process your credit card information.
Shipping: We integrate with a number of shipping
companies to fulfill your orders, primarily with USPS and UPS.
Email: We integrate with approved services to process
newsletters and email updates
Partnering with highly specialized external companies allows us to
focus on what we do best:
selling great products.
How can you control
your personal data?
If you are one of our customers who is in the EU, and we are
specifically selling our products to the
Member State where you are located, you have specific rights that we
are honored to enforce
without undue delay: Access, Correct, Erasure, Port, Object. If you
cannot exercise your choice on
your account page or if you do not have an account with us, please
reach out to us, at the contact
details at the bottom of this page. We will be more than happy to help.
How long do we keep
your data?
We keep your data for as long as you have an account with us. We also
keep some data for security
investigation. Most importantly, we have specific obligations for fraud
detection and tax reasons.
Therefore, we might need to retain certain data even if you ask to
delete it.
Who can you reach
out to for privacy matters?
You can contact our Data Protection Officer here:
privacy@toywiz.com
363 Spook Rock Rd building k
Suffern, NY 10901
Any update?
If we update our Privacy Policy to reflect a change or improvement of
our services or a new legal
obligation, we will publish the new version on our website, and we will
make it clear on our home
page https://www.toywiz.com so it will be visible as you enter our
store.
Protecting
Your Information
Safe & secure shopping is our #1 priority.
We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated
encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your
personal information. Your personal information is contained behind
heavily secured networks. All credit card and personal information you
supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then
encrypted into our databases.
Collecting
Information
Unless otherwise noted or you provide us with
specific information about yourself, we do not gather personal
information. You can visit any of our web pages without telling us who
you are. We will only request information from you when you decide to
place an order, if you decide to participate in a sweepstakes or opt in
for our newsletter..
Sharing
Information
Toywiz.com takes the sharing of your information
seriously.
You are under no obligation to register with the
site in order to access or use this service.
If you do register with this website, you agree to: (a) provide true,
accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted
by the registration form (collectively, "Registration Data"); and (b)
maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it accurate,
current and complete. In addition to and without limiting in any way
the Company's general right to terminate your access and use of the
Services, or the Services themselves, as set forth herein, if you
provide any information determined by the Company, in its sole
discretion, to be untrue, inaccurate, not current, incomplete,
misleading or designed to deceive, or if the Company, in its sole
discretion, believes it has a basis to suspect that such is the case,
the Company has the right to immediately suspend or terminate your
account, either with or without notice to you, and refuse to grant any
and all current or future access and use of the Services (or any
portion thereof) and/or any benefit to which you may be entitled
through your access and use of the Services. You also agree that you
are solely and completely responsible and liable for any and all
activities which occur under your account. In addition, when you
register for the Services, you agree to receive an email newsletter
that may contain the Company and/or Sponsor offers. You may opt-out of
receiving this email newsletter at any time by following the opt-out
instructions provided in the email newsletter.
Newsletter Opt-In and Third Party Offers.
You are not obligated to opt-in to receive the Company's Newsletter. If
you do opt-in to receive the Company's Newsletter you also agree to
receive select ToyWiz Sponsor offers, that will be designated as such.
However, if you choose to opt-out to receive the Newsletter you will
stop receiving the Company's news letter promptly, Howerver, you
understand and agree that select Toy Wiz Sponsor's may contact you
using the registration information you provide to the Company,
including without limitation, by telephone or email, pursuant to the
terms and conditions of the Company's Privacy Policy. The Company
reserves the right to update or modify the number and/or mix of
Sponsors' offers, at any time for any reason, in its sole discretion.
To opt-out of receiving select Toy Wiz Sponsors' offers please follow
the opt-out instructions associated with the Sponsors' offer. Official
Sweepstakes Rules.
You understand, acknowledge and agree to be bound by the relevant
Official Sweepstakes Rules for the sweepstakes you elect to participate
in. Compliance with Order Investigations.
On rare occasions, when credit card fraud is involved we may share
information with companies assisting in the investigation. This is done
for the sole purpose of protecting our rights and the security of
others.
Questions
and Feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns
about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback
pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Copyright
Information
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos,
button icons & images is the property of ToyWiz or its content
suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright
laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive
property of ToyWiz and protected by U.S. and international copyright
laws.
Terms
of Use
By accepting these Terms of Use through your use of the Site, you
certify that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age
of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the
supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by
these Terms of Use. ToyWiz.com does not intentionally collect personal
information about children under the age of 13. Children under the age
of 13 may not use this Site other than for browsing, and parents or
legal guardians may not agree to these Terms of Use on their behalf. If
you are a parent or legal guardian agreeing to these Terms of Use for
the benefit of a child between the ages of 13 and 18, be advised that
you are fully responsible for his or her use of this Site, including
all financial charges and legal liability that he or she may incur. If
you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of these terms and
conditions, do not use this Site. All billing and registration
information provided must be truthful and accurate. Providing any
untruthful or inaccurate information may constitute a breach of these
Terms of Use. By confirming your purchase at the end of the checkout
process, you agree to accept and pay for the item(s) requested.
Any dispute arising from the use of this site, or transaction with this
site, is binding to the state of New York.
Quantity
Limits & Dealer Sales
ToyWiz.com reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to limit the
quantity of items purchased per person, per household or per order.
These restrictions may be applicable to orders placed by the same
credit card and also to orders that use the same billing and/or
shipping address. We will provide notification to the customer should
such limits be applied to an existing order.
Pricing
Information
While ToyWiz.com strives to provide accurate product and pricing
information, pricing or typographical errors may occur. ToyWiz.com
cannot confirm the price of an item until after you order. In the event
that an item is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect
information due to an error in pricing or product information,
ToyWiz.com shall have the right, at our sole discretion, to refuse or
cancel any orders placed for the item. In the event that an item is
mispriced, ToyWiz.com may, at our discretion, either contact you for
instructions or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation.
Mint
Product Policy & Guarantee
ToyWiz.com prides itself on quality. All figures & toys we sell
are guaranteed authentic and "Mint in Sealed Box". This means that the
package or box may have minor wear but the toy inside is always
guaranteed in mint condition, never touched or played with.
Privacy Policy
PLEASE NOTE: THE SERVICES ON THIS WEBSITE ARE ONLY AVAILABLE TO
INDIVIDUALS 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER (INDIVIDUALS UNDER THE AGE OF 18,
THOUGH, MUST OBTAIN THE PERMISSION OF A PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN). IF
YOU DO NOT QUALIFY UNDER THESE REQUIREMENTS, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO
USE OR SUBMIT ANY INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE OR USE THE SERVICE.
Welcome to Toywiz.com website and the services available through this
website (collectively, the "Website" or "Service(s)"). Throughout this
policy, the Company shall be referred to as "Company," "we" or "us".
The website user will be referred to as "You", "User(s)", "Consumer(s)"
or "Subscriber(s)".
This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers the treatment of
personally identifiable information that the Company collects when you
are on the Website and/or when you sign up for and/or use the Service.
It is important that our users are fully informed about the use of
their personal information. The Company believes in 100%
permission-based marketing. This Privacy Policy also applies to
consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from the Company
and the Company's joint marketing advertisers ("Advertisers"), whether
at the Website, via e-mail and/or on third-party websites (via
co-registration or otherwise).
Collection of Information by the Company
Children's Privacy
This Website is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do
not knowingly collect personal information on this Website from
children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have
inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the
age of 13, we will delete the information from our records.
Personally Identifiable Information For each user, our
web server automatically recognizes the user's domain name and IP
address, but not the e-mail address (unless supplied independently by a
user).
To qualify to receive access to the Website and/or Services, subject to
the requirements set forth in our EULA and Website Terms and
Conditions, we gather personal information from you in order to
establish your Company membership account. This information may
include, but is not necessarily limited to, your first and last name,
e-mail address, postal mailing address, mobile telephone number and
other demographic information, as well as credit/debit card information
for payment and/or age verification purposes (collectively, "Personally
Identifiable Information" or "PII". IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOU SUPPLY US
WITH VALID, COMPLETE, CURRENT AND ACCURATE PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE
INFORMATION; SUCH PII WILL BE USED TO SUPPLY THE SERVICES TO YOU AND TO
COLLECT PAYMENT FOR SUCH SERVICES (WHERE APPLICABLE). By submitting
your PII, you authorize us to confirm the accuracy of the information
you submitted against government-issued identification. We may also
collect information related to your online activities to more
accurately target and measure our advertising inventory, including,
without limitation, the places you visit at the Website, content
accessed and associated marketing metrics (such as e-mails opened and
responded to) (collectively, your "Marketing Profile"). In addition, if
you choose to participate in any offer(s) available at or through the
Website, whether offered by us and/or a third party, any Personally
Identifiable Information submitted by you shall be subject to the
privacy policy(s) of the respective third party(s) collecting such PII.
In addition, you may find links to other websites from our Website.
Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy
practices of any third parties and/or websites. We strongly encourage
you to be aware of when you leave our Website and/or supply your
Personally Identifiable Information to any third party, and to read the
privacy policies of each and every third party and/or website before
using such third party website(s) and/or before supplying any PII to
them. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by
this Website.
Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information Obtained by Company
You understand and agree that the Company may use and share your PII
with third parties as needed to supply the Service(s) to you. For
example, if you want to use a ringtone that you created on your mobile
device, we will transfer your mobile telephone number and the location
of the ringtone to a service provider, who will then transmit the
ringtone to your mobile device for your personal use.
You understand and agree our advertising relationships allow us to make
the Company, its Website and/or the Service(s) available to you.
Accordingly, the Personally Identifiable Information that you submit to
the Company remains your property, but by participating in the Company
Website and/or Service(s), you grant us the right to use such PII and
your Marketing Profile for multiple marketing purposes, including, but
not limited to, sharing such PII with third parties. The Company may
use such Personally Identifiable Information to (i) directly market
certain offers to you via e-mail marketing, telemarketing, direct mail,
mobile telephone text messaging (including, without limitation, SMS
and/or MMS) and other methods, (ii) to monitor compliance with our
Website EULA and Terms and Conditions, and (iii) for content
improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell your Personally
Identifiable Information that you supply to us and we may join together
with other third-party businesses to bring selected retail
opportunities to you. These businesses may include, but are not limited
to, providers of online, e-mail, telemarketing and direct mail
marketing services and applications. Such services and applications may
include, but not be limited to, lookup and reference, data enhancement,
overlay, appending, suppression and validation. By registering for
toywiz.com, you are indicating that you have read and agree to this
Privacy Policy and of its all terms and conditions, and you further
acknowledge and agree that you understand how and under what
circumstances your Personally Identifiable Information will be used.
You also agree to receive marketing promotions and other solicitations
from this Website, its advertising partners and/or other third-party
advertisers (collectively, "Website Sponsors") based on the PII you
provide on this Website, and expressly agree to be contacted by any
such Website Sponsors through direct mail, phone, pre-recorded message,
SMS text and/or email. In addition to marketing purposes, the Company
reserves the right to release your Personally Identifiable Information
if: (a) we believe that the Website and/or Service(s) is being or has
been used in violation of the EULA and/or Terms and Conditions and/or
to commit unlawful acts; (b) your Personally Identifiable Information
is subpoenaed or requested by a court, governmental agency or law
enforcement entity; or (c) the Company is sold, transferred and/or
acquired. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any
information, record or communication from you to any third party when
the Company determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure is
appropriate or necessary, for example, to share your e-mail address
with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with
the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. In addition,
you agree that by registering for a Company membership, such act
constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes of the
Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR 310 et seq. ("Rule").
Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal
Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, the Company retains the right to
contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule. Moreover, by
registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party
advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute an
inquiry and/or application with the respective third-party advertiser
for purposes of the Rule. As such, you may be contacted via e-mail,
direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in
accordance with the Rule. To the extent that your credit card-specific
information and/or social security number is collected by the Company,
said information will be transmitted securely, kept in confidence and
will not be shared with any third parties (other than third party
service providers - such as payment processors - who provide services
to the Company and/or consumer credit agencies) without your prior
informed consent. In addition, by submitting your credit card
information to us, you authorize the Company to periodically verify by
various methods that your credit card account continues to be valid and
active, including, without limitation, charging and thereafter
immediately crediting a small sum to the credit card. Apart from the
foregoing uses, the Company and its affiliates and/or subsidiaries
reserve the right to share with third parties the fact that we/they
have credit card information on file for you, but such specific credit
card information shall not be shared by us/them with any third parties
without your prior authorization.
You may receive an e-mail confirming your membership with the Company,
co-registration with Advertisers, as well as promotional marketing of
commercial products and services. The Company reserves the right to
collect and retain data relating to e-mail marketing sent to, and
opened by, individuals on our marketing list(s).
Opt-Out Policy
You may exercise your option to not receive any future communications
from us by clicking here. Subscribers should note that unsubscribing
from this Website's electronic mailings will not automatically
unsubscribe you from any communications you have elected to receive
from our Clients or other third parties. Please note that you may still
receive information from third parties to whom we have disclosed your
Personally Identifiable Information prior to the time you opted-out.
The Company Website users who no longer wish to receive promotional
e-mail materials from our Advertisers may opt-out of receiving these
communications by following the instructions contained in the
applicable e-mail, in accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. You
must unsubscribe separately from each Advertiser's list. To unsubscribe
from any Advertiser's website or e-mail list, please visit their
website or review their e-mail for complete "unsubscribe" details.
Similarly, if, after unsubscribing from Company emails, you click on or
access an Advertiser's offer appearing at the Website, you may begin
receiving offers by, or on behalf of, those particular Advertisers. You
must unsubscribe from their list in order to stop receiving their email
offers.
Privacy Complaints
If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy,
please contact us at: privacy@toywiz.com.
Please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you
believe that this Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will
investigate and respond to your complaint as promptly as possible under
the circumstances.
If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed,
you may contact the Direct Marketing Association at
privacypromise@the-dma.org or in writing at:
Direct Marketing Association: Attn: Privacy Promise, 615 L St. NW,
Suite 1100, Washington, DC 20036
How to Access or Modify Your Information
We strive to keep all Personally Identifiable Information current,
accurate and complete. You are always fully in control of the PII that
we maintain to service you. You can change your PII at any time and as
often as necessary. You can also request that any Personally
Identifiable Information be deleted. Certain Personally Identifiable
Information may be withheld or exempted from deletion if this is
required by law or is part of a fraud investigation, or as otherwise
described above in the "Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information
Obtained By Company" section.
You may access and modify your Personally Identifiable Information by
contacting us at: privacy@toywiz.com
Special Notification for California Residents
Individuals who reside in California and have provided their Personally
Identifiable Information may request information regarding disclosures
of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.
Such requests must be submitted to us at the following emailing
address: CAPrivacy@toywiz.com
This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We
reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to
the address specified above.
General information collection and use - Aggregate
We gather our users' server, IP address and browser-type related
information in the general administration of our Website and
Service(s). The Company reserves the right to transfer and/or sell
aggregate or group data about the Company users for lawful purposes.
Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage
or other characteristics of the Company's users as a group, without
disclosing Personally Identifiable Information. By submitting your
Personally Identifiable Information to, and/or using, the Website
and/or Service(s), you agree to allow the Company to transfer and/or
sell such aggregate data to third parties.
Log Files
Like most website servers, we use log files. Log files include internet
protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP),
referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of
clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in
the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate
use. Log file information is not linked to Personally Identifiable
Information.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a text file stored on a user's hard drive containing
information about the respective user. Cookies can provide great
convenience for users at many websites and is required to use the
Company Website and Service(s). For instance, by associating a cookie
with your computer which is identified and processed by our servers,
you need not log in more than once at the Website, thereby saving time
and convenience while using our servers. In particular, we may use
persistent and/or session cookies at the Website. Persistent cookies do
not automatically expire, but persist to permit the Company to register
future visits at the Website with your profile in our servers. In
addition, cookies associated with the Company may be read, aggregated
and used with cookies associated with other affiliate Internet
properties.
In addition, we and/or third parties that advertise at the Website and
through other types of media available at or through the Website may
use cookies and pixel gifs to track and target the interests of our
users to enhance the experience on our Website and/or for advertising
tracking purposes.
Third Party Cookies
The Company delivers to your web browser many of the advertisements you
see when you use the Website. However, the Company also allows other
companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve
advertisements within and/or on the Website. Because your web browser
must request these advertising banners from the ad networks' servers,
these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as
if you had requested a web page from the Website. Please note that if
an Advertiser asks the Company to show an advertisement to a certain
audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for
example, men ages 13-24 who have viewed sports content) and you respond
to that ad, the Advertiser and/or ad-server may conclude that you fit
the description of the audience they are trying to reach. However, the
Company only authorizes our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous
cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. To the Company's
knowledge, the third-party ad servers do not collect Personally
Identifiable Information about you. In addition, the Company uses
third-party service provider partners to employ anonymous cookies for
accounting and data integrity purposes. If you want to prevent a
third-party ad server and/or third-party service provider from sending
and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad
network's and service provider's website individually and opt-out (if
they offer this capability).
Currently, we have relationships with third party service providers
and/or may display third party ad server networks (click to
visit their website). In addition, we may at some point
engage other third-party ad servers and/or third-party service
providers in the future.
You can set your browser to accept all cookies, to notify you when a
cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. Each browser
is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to
change your cookie preferences. For further information on cookies
please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org.
Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the
correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical,
electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
information we collect online. Although we take reasonable
technological precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable
Information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed
to be 100% secure. When a user submits sensitive personal and payment
information via the Website, the information is protected both online
and off-line. When our registration, download or purchase process
prompts a user to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card
number), the information is encrypted and is protected with
industry-standard encryption - SSL technology. While we use SSL
encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also use
commercially reasonable measures to protect user information off-line.
Access to user information is restricted in our offices and areas where
such information is stored. Only employees and authorized individuals
who need access to the information to perform a specific job are
granted access to Personally Identifiable Information. If you have any
questions about the security at our Website, please contact us at
security@toywiz.com.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion and at any time, to
change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. All
Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting
on the Website. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your
continued use of the Company Website and/or Service(s) following the
posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance
of such changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy
Policy, you may not use and/or access the Website and/or Service(s).
Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy
By using this Website and/or Service(s), you agree to all of the terms
and conditions of the Company Privacy Policy, as well as all other
policies contained on the Website and relating to the Services.
Questions? Contact us
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings
with the service, please do not hesitate to contact us at:
ToyWiz.com
363 Spook Rock, Building K
Suffern, NY 109011.
Your cart is empty.
